

Shanghai, China +86 186 1675 0412 sayidhrq@gmail.com www.sayidhe.com

BIOGRAPHY

I am a Chinese designer specializing in UI/UX and Front-end. I have 5+ years design experiences on a digital product. Besides design beautiful things through sketch and photoshop, I also love using Linux/RaspberryPi/Github to building some interesting open source stuff.

Bē sayidhrq

8

ruiquan.he

n Sayid He

EXPERIENCE

DESIGNER

Archex | May, 2016 - Apr, 2018

Designer at ArcheX - Food, Digital and Business Innovation. Learning lot of design thinking and design sprint.

WEB/UX DESIGNER

altima° | Fab, 2014 - Jan, 2016

Main designer at altima° agency of Shanghai as UI and UX designer. Specialize at E-Commerce.

WEB/VISUAL DESIGNER

Tencent Fuzhou Branch | May, 2013 - Jan, 2014

Work as Junior Designer at Tencent Fuzhou Branch, more focus on visual design and user experience design.

PROJECTS

INNOVATION PROJCETS

24 Solar Food

DIGITAL PLATFORM PROJCETS

Farm Window / Engaging

OFFICIAL WEBSITE PROJECT

Archex Official Website / Project A1 / Amcham_HK / Beijing World Young Academy / ESSEC Business School

E-COMMERCE PROJECT

Bioderma / ClubMed / Decathlon / Novotal / Bon TV / Hutong School / Lantern

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Air Pollution Notifier / My Personal Website / My Personal Blog

EDUCATION

DIGITAL MEDIA ART

Fuzhou University | Sep, 2008 - May, 2013

Learning digital media art at Fuzhou University and got Bachelor's degree after graduated from college.

SKILLS

Sketch

Photoshop

Illustrator

Framerjs

CSS/HTML/JS

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Chinese native speaker, fluent at English speaking and writing. And learned little French from former colleagues.



ENGLISH 80%

FRENCH 10%

